{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","address":"205 W Congress","zipcode":"4821","owner":"Essex Alliance USA Holdings","licenseNumber":"229256","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"7/12/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E610000058F1407614C354C0B88569DD1B2A4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43857","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","inspectionDate":"2018-10-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43857","inspectionDate":"10/24/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"6-302.11","violationDescription":"A supply of toilet tissue shall be available at each toilet.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Toilet paper","subItem":"at toilet in restroom men's","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"43857","inspectionDate":"10/24/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"43615","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","inspectionDate":"2018-09-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inspectorid":"122","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43615","inspectionDate":"9/14/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"VENTILATION HOOD SYSTEM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."}]},{"inspectionid":"43154","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","inspectionDate":"2018-07-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inspectorid":"122","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"8","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"8","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43154","inspectionDate":"7/9/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"10 foot candles","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Light intensity","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"43154","inspectionDate":"7/9/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"SIGNAGE","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"43154","inspectionDate":"7/9/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43154","inspectionDate":"7/9/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Open seams","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"Facility","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"43154","inspectionDate":"7/9/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Paper toweling","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate sanitary hand drying aids/devices."},{"inspectionid":"43154","inspectionDate":"7/9/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Soap","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate supply of soap at all hand sinks."},{"inspectionid":"43154","inspectionDate":"7/9/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"inspectionid":"43154","inspectionDate":"7/9/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With ledges, projections, or crevices","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"43154","inspectionDate":"7/9/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."},{"inspectionid":"43154","inspectionDate":"7/9/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Floor material(s)","subItem":"for construction","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"Floor sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"43154","inspectionDate":"7/9/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622749","name":"Trust Night Club","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Ice machine","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"AIR GAP","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622749"}}